http://www.mercuryperformance.com/privacypolicy

Privacy Policy
Effective October 29th, 2013 this privacy statement describes how Performance Marine collects
and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: mercuryperformance.com. It also describes
the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access
and update this information.If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first contact us at info@mercuryperformance.com. If you do not receive acknowledgment of
your inquiry, or if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed you should then call us
at 877-810-7779 for more information.We collect the following personal information from you:Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone numberBilling Information such as credit card number, and billing addressUnique Identifiers such as user name, account number, passwordPreferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferencesWe also collect the following information from you:Information about your business such as company name, company size, business typeAs is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP
address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.We use this information to:Fulfill your orderSend you an order confirmationAssess the needs of your business to determine suitable productsSend you requested product or service informationSend product updates or warranty informationRespond to customer service requestsAdminister your accountSend you a newsletterSend you marketing communicationsRespond to your questions and concernsImprove our Web site and marketing effortsConduct research and analysisCHOICE/OPT-OUTYou may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe
instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at info@mercuryperformance.com.INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM THIRD PARTIESWe obtain address information about you from third party sources, such as the US Postal Service,
to verify your address so we can properly ship your order to you and to prevent fraud.We purchase marketing data about our customers from third parties and combine it with
information we already have about you, to create more tailored advertising and products.We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described
in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our
business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies
are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to
provide these services to us.WE MAY ALSO DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONas required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal processwhen we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your
safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,if Performance Marine is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its
assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change
in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding
your personal information,To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.PAYPALIf you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card
number, directly to PayPal. PayPal’s privacy policy will apply to the information you provide
on the PayPal Web site.THIRD PARTY E-MERCHANTOur shopping cart is hosted by e-merchant check out. They host our ordering system, and collect your
billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order. This company does
not use this information for any other purpose.We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies
are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include
personal information.We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable
information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site.WEB BEACONSOur Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.Our Web pages may also contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel
gifs) that are set by our third party partners. Web beacons are used along with cookies enabling our
partners to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used.We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we
will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this
aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITESOur Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of
Performance Marine Online Store. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your
information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy
statement of any Web site you visit.The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry
standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we
receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100%
secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions
about security on our Web site, you can contact us at info@mercuryperformance.com.We provide two means for you to make a purchase on our site. You can either use our order form or a
third party payment option. If you use our shopping cart, the transmission of sensitive information
collected on our order form is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). If you choose
to use a third party payment option to pay for your order, its privacy statement and security
practices will apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before
providing your information.CORRECTING AND UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONTo review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at info@mercuryperformance.com.NOTIFICATION OF PRIVACY STATEMENT CHANGESWe may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any
material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account)
or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to
periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:Performance Marine, Inc.1130 US HWY 27 NorthLake
Placid, FL, United States 33852Email: info@mercuryperformance.comPhone: 877-810-7779
© 2020 Performance Sales & Service - Powered by ARI Network Services - ARI Responsive Websites
Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions
Site Map
